hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨，春季粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装Spring 提示
installment we're going to take a look
分期付款，我们来看看
at the brand new just announced spring
在刚刚宣布的春季新品上
cloud circuit breaker project the whole
整个云断路器项目
point of the circuit breaker project is
断路器项目的重点是
to provide an abstraction on top of well
在井的顶部提供抽象
other circuit breakers certainly
当然其他断路器
including but not limited to Netflix's
包括但不限于Netflix的
hystrix resilience 4j alibaba's Sentinel
hystrix Resilience4J 阿里巴巴的前哨
which I introduced in a previous spring
我在前一个春天介绍的
tips by the way and we also we
技巧，我们也
introduced them hystrix and spring retry
向他们介绍了hystrix和spring retry
so it's a alibaba's Sentinel spring
所以这是阿里巴巴的前哨春天
retried history and resilience for J
J的重试历史记录和恢复力
that are these are the four supported
这些是支持的四个
circuit breakers we've looked at three
我们研究了三个断路器
of those in in previous installments of
前几期中的那些
spring tips where and we looked at
春天的提示，我们在哪里看
circuit breakers generally with hystrix
一般带有hystrix的断路器
and spring we tried a few years ago and
春天我们几年前尝试过
then more recently looked at alibaba's
然后最近看了阿里巴巴的
spring cloud integration now these
春季云集成现在这些
different technologies can be used with
可以使用不同的技术
instrument cloud from a unified
统一的工具云
abstraction thanks to this new project
这个新项目带来了抽象
that we've just announced that supports
我们刚刚宣布支持
both reactive and nonreactive sort of
反应性和非反应性的
use cases it's not yet GA so we're gonna
用例还不是通用航空，所以我们要
have to add our dependency Manley but
必须添加我们的依赖Manley，但是
that's not a big deal let's go back to
没什么大不了的，让我们回到
my second favorite place on the Internet
我在互联网上第二喜欢的地方
of course start dead spring that IO and
当然，IO和
we're gonna build a new application here
我们将在这里构建一个新的应用程序
I'm just gonna call this circuit breaker
我要叫这个断路器
okay and we can use two 2.0 snapshot
好的，我们可以使用两个2.0快照
latest and greatest and I'll bring in
最新和最伟大的，我会带来
Lombok coming in the reactive web
龙目岛进入反应网络
support and there is no circuit breaker
支持，没有断路器
dependency not yet anyway so we need to
依赖还没有，所以我们需要
we need to add that manually okay with
我们需要手动添加
this we can go ahead and build an
我们可以继续并建立一个
application I want to have cloud
我想拥有云的应用程序
bootstraps I have that that way it'll
我有那样的引导
give me the spring cloud um dependency
给我春天的乌云依赖
management you know the the maven
管理你知道的行家
repository and the bomb and all their
储存库和炸弹及其所有
stuff so I can just add the dependency I
东西，所以我可以添加依赖项
need for for a spring hot circuit
需要Spring 热回路
breaker and I don't have to worry about
断路器，我不必担心
the rest all right
剩下的没事
that's there open up a shell here CD
在那打开一个外壳
downloads ueo a circuit breaker
下载ueo断路器
all right and we're just gonna add the
好的，我们将添加
one dependency that we need so I'm gonna
我们需要的一种依赖，所以我要
go to Palm the next ml and we're just
下一个毫升去棕榈吧，我们只是
going to add the zero zero you know one
要添加零零，你知道一个
snapshot version of the spring cloud
春天云的快照版本
start a circuit breaker project
启动断路器项目
okay so dependencies spring cloud
好吧，依存关系春天云
circuit breaker resilience for J so
J so的断路器弹性
we're gonna bring we're gonna bring in
我们要带我们来
the resilience for J implementation
J实施的弹性
that'll of course in turn transitively
当然，这将反过来
bring in everything else we need I
带来我们需要的其他一切
neglected to specify Java eleven back at
忽略了指定Java十一点
the spring initializer so I'll do that
春天的初始化器，所以我会做
right here and I'm gonna hit maven
就在这里，我要打Maven
re-import bringing all the dependencies
重新导入带来所有依赖
forced to refresh its understanding of
被迫重新了解
the layout of my dependency management
我的依赖管理的布局
graph okay and then we're gonna go to
图好，然后我们去
our program and so we're gonna do is
我们的程序，所以我们要做的是
going to build a simple application that
将要构建一个简单的应用程序
has a web endpoint and that webbing
有一个Web端点和那个织带
point will act as the client we can use
点将充当我们可以使用的客户端
that to invoke and observe behavior in
在其中调用和观察行为
the system but it in turn will call
系统，但依次会调用
something that will will that will fail
将会失败的东西
right it'll call a service now I could
正确，现在我可以打电话给服务了
create and network circles I could
建立和建立社交圈
create another service and make this a
创建另一个服务并使它成为
client that talks to another thing over
谈论另一件事的客户
the network but there's really no need
网络，但实际上没有必要
because all I need to care about here is
因为我需要关心的是
the the behavior of the client with
客户的行为
respect to some other thing right so if
尊重其他事情，如果
that client throws an exception who
该客户抛出异常
cares whether that exception is because
关心那个例外是否是因为
of a network call or whatever right so
网络通话或其他任何正确的方式
in the circuit breaker doesn't care it
在断路器不在乎
just knows that you're calling something
只是知道你在打电话
that might fail as far as its concerned
就其而言可能会失败
it could be anything right so we're
可能什么都对，所以我们
gonna start with a very simple feeling
从一个非常简单的感觉开始
service okay class feeling service and
服务还可以，班级感觉服务和
make this a service bean thanks so all
使它成为服务bean非常感谢
right and our feeling service is going
对，我们的感觉服务正在发展
to we're going to use it to generate a
我们将使用它来生成一个
string a greeting of some sort of a
串起某种问候
publisher string
发布者字符串
okay and actually it could be a mono I
好吧，实际上这可能是我的单声道
suppose it could be a mono that's good
假设它可能是一个很好的单声道
yeah so let's just do greet string name
是的，让我们来问候一下字符串名称
but you know the name could be it could
但你知道名字可能是
be let's make the name optional I want
让我们将名称设为可选
the name to be something that you can
可以做的名字
either specify or not so that we have a
指定或不指定，以便我们有一个
way of introducing variability and
引入可变性的方式
triggering an exception okay you
触发异常好吗
wouldn't normally design a program that
通常不会设计一个程序
fails if you have an optional that it
如果您有一个可选的选项，它将失败
returns nothing that's the whole point
不返回全部内容
of an optional but I want to use that as
可选，但我想将其用作
a way for us to to force this program to
我们强制该程序的一种方式
throw an exception under a certain
在一定条件下抛出异常
condition and that condition will be if
条件，该条件将是
there is no value in the name so what
名称中没有任何价值
we're gonna do is going to say that we
我们要做的就是说我们
have a return value or a URL or a
具有返回值或URL或
greeting I guess so far greeting equals
问候，我猜到目前为止，问候等于
name dot map and we're gonna basically
命名点图，我们基本上
say okay if the string is there then we
说好，如果字符串在那里，那么我们
say hello string okay or else or else
打个招呼字符串好吧，否则
well I guess it's it actually we want to
好吧，我想这就是我们真正想要的
return to publish or don't we so we want
返回发布还是我们不这样做，所以我们想要
to return a publisher with that string
返回带有该字符串的发布者
so mono dot just okay there is this or
所以单点就可以了
else mono dot error all right so we're
否则单点错误就可以了
going to throw an exception in the
将在
pipeline if you don't return if you
如果您不返回，则管道
don't provide a string it could be any
不提供字符串，可以是任何字符串
exception I'm using no point two
例外，我没有使用第二点
exceptions because it's an exception
例外，因为这是一个例外
that's on hand it doesn't really matter
就在眼前，这并不重要
what we use and so I guess I just want
我们使用什么，所以我想我只想要
to turn that I don't even need to have
让我什至不需要
the intermediate variable do I so I
我是中间变量吗
could say return alright good stuff all
可以说归还好东西
right so there's my little service now
对，所以现在有我的小服务
let's build an endpoint a HTTP endpoint
让我们建立一个HTTP端点
that will in turn call that and that
依次将其称为
will depend upon the the behavior okay
取决于行为还可以
so we'll create a rescue scroller here
所以我们在这里创建一个救援卷轴
and I'm using a reactive API is here but
我在这里使用反应式API，但是
it is
它是
it's the same idea you could actually
这是你实际上可以想到的想法
return you can use the nonreactive
返回可以使用非反应性
circuit breaker support as well there's
断路器支持以及
a separate type and I'll show you to
一个单独的类型，我将告诉您
show you where that would look a little
告诉你看起来会在哪里
different but it doesn't matter right it
不同但没关系吧
it's actually more interesting for me
实际上对我来说更有趣
that this works nicely for reactive code
这对于反应式代码很好
but they both supported okay so rest
但是他们都支持，所以休息
controller okay and what are we gonna do
控制器好，我们该怎么办
we are going to have a constructor so
我们将要有一个构造函数
I'm gonna say private final failing
我要说私​​人决赛失败
service okay and I'm going to have a
服务还可以，我要去
constructor that injects the feelings
注入情感的构造函数
service all right okay and we're gonna
服务还好吧，我们要
have a an endpoint date get mapping that
有一个端点日期得到映射
is called wheat so publisher of type
被称为小麦，所以类型的发布者
string tweaked and we're gonna take
调整弦，我们要
optional we'll take an optional request
可选，我们将接受可选请求
parameter right so you give us a name
参数正确，所以你给我们起个名字
we're gonna pass that down to the
我们将把它传递给
underlying service okay
基础服务还可以
good stuff and we're gonna say returned
好东西，我们要说回来了
this that feeling service dot greet
感觉服务点打招呼
passing on the name so you know if you
传递名字，所以你知道你是否
said if you make a request an HTTP GET
表示如果您请求HTTP GET
request to four slash greet question
请求以四个斜杠打招呼
mark name equals you know four bar it'll
标记名称等于您知道四个小节
call this and that'll be okay right
打电话给我就可以了
if you return if you just save for such
如果你回来，如果你只是保存这样的
we'd without the parameter well of
我们会没有很好的参数
course we know that battle results in a
当然，我们知道战斗会导致
null pointer exception right mono two
空指针异常对单二
error no pointer so we want to protect
错误没有指针，所以我们要保护
against this failing and so here's a
针对这种失败，所以这是一个
great example of where we could use a
我们可以在哪里使用的一个很好的例子
circuit breaker so we're going to inject
断路器，所以我们要注入
our circuit breaker factory and there's
我们的断路器工厂，还有
actually two bearings there's a circuit
实际上两个轴承有一个电路
breaker factory or the reactive circuit
断路器工厂或无功电路
breaker factory okay so
断路器工厂可以吗
of course naturally I'm going to inject
当然我自然要注入
the reactive one okay there's this and
反应性好吧，这就是
private final circuit breaker or is it
专用最终断路器还是它
reactive circuit breaker right this tool
无功断路器对这个工具
in there good so we'll use the circuit
在那里好，所以我们将使用电路
breaker factory to create an instance
断路器工厂创建实例
and then stash it okay I'm just gonna be
然后藏起来好吧，我会成为
called wheat and we can now wrap this
叫做小麦，我们现在可以把它包起来
thing that returns a publisher our
回报出版商的东西
results equals this right that's a cold
结果等于这个权利，这很冷
stream right now right we haven't
现在还没有流
actually executed it we haven't
实际上执行了我们没有
subscribed to it and so it doesn't do
订阅了它，所以它没有做
anything yet
还没有
so we can say we turn this dot circuit
所以可以说我们把这个点电路
breaker dot run we're just past the cold
断路器点跑，我们刚过去的寒冷
stream and it'll apply the default
流，它将应用默认
configuration for all circuit breakers
所有断路器的配置
in the system before I provide a
在系统中，我提供一个
fallback behavior we can use we can
我们可以使用的后备行为
provide a function that looks like this
提供看起来像这样的功能
okay so the idea is that given an
好吧，所以想法是
exception of some sort we return a
某种异常，我们返回一个
publisher of string all right so we
字符串的发布者可以，所以我们
could just you know mono just hello
你能知道单声道吗
world all right eventually nice lambda
最终世界还不错lambda
all right so there's our there's our
好吧，有我们的有我们的
greetings endpoint and our failing
问候端点和我们的失败
service that makes the network that
使网络能够
could make it recall using the reactive
可以使它使用反应式
web client or or our sockets our socket
Web客户端或我们的套接字
requester or whatever right I'm sure you
请求者或其他任何我可以肯定的权利
can imagine how you would make a
可以想象你会如何
reactive web call at this point that's
此时的响应式网络通话是
not the point of this video now a couple
现在不是这个视频的重点
things to keep in mind that circuit
电路要记住的事情
breaker here is using greet as a string
这里的断路器使用greet作为字符串
it's an arbitrary stream you I've given
这是我给你的任意信息流
it a name so that you can then define
它的名字，这样你就可以定义
configuration for it somewhere else
在其他地方进行配置
right so you can actually configure the
正确，因此您可以实际配置
specifics of the circuit breaker
断路器的细节
bye-bye that string ID so that's how you
再见那个字符串ID，这就是你的方式
link this circuit breaker to
将此断路器链接到
configuration that you would define
您将定义的配置
elsewhere we haven't specified any
其他地方我们还没有指定
configuration so we get the default sort
配置，以便我们获得默认排序
of generic global configuration let's
通用全局配置让我们
see what this looks like okay let's see
看看这看起来怎么样，让我们​​看看
what that looks like right now localhost
现在看起来像什么localhost
wait name equals taja
等待名称等于taja
okay so we got and then Bob there's a
好吧，我们得到了，然后鲍勃，有一个
it's working okay now what if we dropped
现在可以了如果我们掉线怎么办
the name hello world right the circuit
你好世界的名字正确的电路
breaker was invoked so you can see
调用了断路器，因此您可以看到
that's pretty interesting right we get
那很有趣，我们得到了
some some very simple behavior here but
一些一些非常简单的行为，但是
we can see how it's working now the
我们可以看到它现在如何工作
circuit breaker is pretty it's doing the
断路器很漂亮，它正在做
right thing right we're getting our
对的事情对了，我们正在得到我们的
default fallback we're controlling how
默认回退，我们控制着
the service fails and we're able to
服务失败，我们能够
behave or to add some other behavior as
表现或添加一些其他行为
we need to and we just wrap it with this
我们需要，我们只是用这个包装
little lambda it's very very simple to
小lambda，这非常简单
do that okay so I like that but I want
这样做可以，所以我喜欢，但是我想要
to configure it I want to override some
配置它，我想覆盖一些
configuration here and specify for
在这里配置并指定
example how a circuit breaker behaves if
例如，如果
for example is a pathway that's being
例如，一条正在被
invoked takes too long okay I want to
调用花费的时间太长了，我想
configure the default behavior for that
为此配置默认行为
so what I'm going to do is I'm gonna
所以我要做的是
override the default resent reactive
覆盖默认的重发反应
resilience forge a circuit breaker
弹性锻造断路器
factory I'll provide the beam okay
工厂我会提供光束的
like so so I can I can react reasons for
这样我就可以回应原因
J Sikora factory so there's my factory
J Sikora工厂，所以有我的工厂
factory equals this and I want to
工厂等于这个，我想
configure some things before I get too
我也要先配置一些东西
far down the line so that you can
很远的地方，以便您可以
override that you can do that for you
覆盖您可以为您做到的
know all the factories I'm gonna
知道我要去的所有工厂
overwrite it for this and I can just can
为此覆盖它，我可以
configure things on this as well so I
以及在此配置的东西，所以我
wanna configure the default behavior for
要配置默认行为
example and the way you do that is you
例子，而你这样做的方式就是你
are given a string which corresponds to
给出一个对应于的字符串
the ID that's to be configured and you
要配置的ID，您
provide a configuration using the config
使用config提供配置
builder and so I and when to build a new
建造者，所以我以及何时建造新的
resilience Forge a config builder
弹性打造配置构建器
passing in the ID that I've been given
传递我得到的ID
that's s and then I'll called that built
那是s，然后我将其称为
and I have some options here I have some
我这里有一些选择
options to specify for example time
指定时间的选项
limiter so time limiter config that
限制器，所以时间限制器配置，
custom duck-billed and I'm going to
自定义鸭嘴，我要去
specify the timeout duration and the
指定超时时间和
duration I'm going to specify is five
我要指定的持续时间是五
seconds all right so I'm gonna say that
没问题，所以我要说
I will in after five seconds if an
我会在五秒钟后
endpoint that I'm calling takes longer
我正在呼叫的端点需要更长的时间
than five seconds which is a
超过五秒钟
preposterous lay long amount of time you
荒谬的时间很长
shouldn't have anything hopefully taking
应该没有什么希望
five seconds but if you do this will
五秒钟，但如果这样做
trigger the circuit breaker and you'll
触发断路器，您将
get the default fallback behavior which
获取默认的后备行为
is what you want in this case we also
在这种情况下就是您想要的
want some circuit breaker config we can
想要一些断路器配置，我们可以
just use the circuit breaker config
只需使用断路器配置
default right so there you go and of
默认的权利，所以你去和
course this lends itself to lambda good
当然这很适合lambda
stuff okay so this my default
东西还好，所以这是我的默认设置
configuration now I did so you can
现在我做了配置，所以您可以
configure specific circuit breakers as
将特定的断路器配置为
well so you could say factory dot
好吧，你可以说工厂点
configure and there the second parameter
配置第二个参数
is a Varitek array of string IDs okay
是字符串ID的Varitek数组吗
these are the IDs to which this
这些是这个的ID
configuration should apply so you could
配置应适用，以便您可以
say Greek you could provide a
说希腊语，您可以提供
configuration there just like I did for
就像我所做的那样在那里进行配置
the default and then specify Greek as
默认值，然后将Greek指定为
the second parameter
第二个参数
and that would have that would mean that
那将意味着
the configuration only applied to that
该配置仅适用于
particular circuit breaker all right so
特定的断路器好吗
now in order first in order for us to
现在为了首先为了我们
see this in action we need to introduce
看到这一点，我们需要介绍
a little bit of time into our into our
一点时间进入我们的
flow here okay so what we're gonna do is
流动在这里好，所以我们要做的是
we're going to delay the publication of
我们将推迟发布
data so we're going to say map this to a
数据，所以我们要说将此映射到
string or else to an error but we want
字符串或其他错误，但我们想要
to delay the elements all right so let's
延迟所有元素，所以让我们
say it's raishin of seconds and we want
说是几秒钟的葡萄干，我们想要
that seconds count to be something that
那秒算是
we arrive at dynamically so again I'm
我们动态到达，所以我再次
I'm doing this to to sort of stub out a
我这样做是为了存根
slowing it recall okay so I'm going to
放慢速度，回想一下，所以我要
say it long math dot random times ten
说长数学点随机十倍
okay so I'm I'm creating a second
好吧，我现在要创建第二个
argument so it's gonna be if it's you
论据，如果是你
know if it's if it's five six seven if
知道是不是五六七，如果
it's you know anything above five or
你知道五岁以上
maybe equal to five then of course it'll
也许等于五那么当然
trigger the circuit breaker otherwise
否则触发断路器
it'll return the normal value okay so
它会返回正常值，所以
we're introducing a delay in how fast
我们引入了延迟速度
this publisher gets published this item
该发布者发布了该项目
gets published
被发表
okay we should actually that's let's
好吧，我们实际上应该让
indicate how long it took and I'll log
指出花了多长时间，我将记录
it out as well so we can see what should
以及它，所以我们可以看到应该
have been returned and what is so far
已经归还，到目前为止
all right no you know what we need to
好吧，不，你知道我们需要什么
put that in here
把它放在这里
okay get rid of that there's this good
好吧，摆脱这个好东西
stuff so now return this give it a nap
东西，所以现在返回这个给它小睡
okay so those are our string I'm
好，那是我们的弦
recording this video on QuickTime so
在QuickTime上录制此视频，以便
it's making my CPU crawl everything is
这使我的CPU抓取所有内容
super slow log4j alright okay so there
超慢的log4j好吧，所以那里
we go now we restart
我们现在去重新启动
okay so that's working name equals Bob
好的，所以工作名称等于Bob
nine seconds so that will trigger the
九秒钟，这将触发
circuit breaker in which you just get
您刚刚在其中得到的断路器
hello world after five seconds right in
五秒钟后进入世界
one second we get it back hello Bob in
一秒钟，我们把它拿回来
one in eight seconds that'll give us how
八分之一秒会告诉我们
the world right because that's more than
世界，因为那不仅仅是
five seconds so there you go
五秒钟，所以你走了
six again we get hello world you can see
六点，我们再次打招呼，你可以看到
them logs that are in the bottom you can
他们在底部的日志，你可以
see what it's trying to prepare for us
看看它正在为我们做些什么
but it takes too long so it's a circuit
但要花很长时间，所以它是一个电路
breakers acting on behalf of the client
代表客户行事的断路器
saying no no I can't wait this long I
说不不，我等不了这么久
gotta go so here's how the world instead
要走了，这就是世界
all right so we can see that the circuit
好的，所以我们可以看到电路
breaker you know it works perfectly
断路器，您知道它运作完美
works nicely it's easily add it to an
效果很好，很容易将其添加到
existing code base it doesn't add much
现有的代码库并不会增加太多
more and wait there's still things still
更多，等等，仍然还有事情
some things that to be done you know I
有些事情要做，你知道我
think there's discussion of discussion
认为有讨论的讨论
around adding support for annotations I
关于添加对注释的支持
don't know I don't know what that would
不知道我不知道那会是什么
look like
看起来像
Ryan Baxter and the team are working on
瑞安·巴克斯特（Ryan Baxter）和团队正在努力
this and are of course always eager to
这当然总是渴望
get the feedback so if you chime in on
得到反馈，所以如果您喜欢
gay issues or if you send the messages
同性恋问题或您是否发送邮件
on the on the git er that I am github
在我是github的git er上
authenticated software community
经过认证的软件社区
community channels that'd be awesome or
很棒的社区频道或
Twitter ad spring cloud there's also
Twitter广告Spring Cloud也有
perhaps the use case for dynamically
也许是动态的用例
yeah you know programmatically adding a
是的，您知道以编程方式添加了一个
saree program programmatically opening
以编程方式打开纱丽程序
and closing the circuit breaker I mean
然后合上断路器
all sorts of interesting possibilities
各种有趣的可能性
beyond this but the the important stuff
除此之外，但重要的东西
is here right now and so this is
现在在这里，所以这是
actually a nice way forward for people
对人们来说实际上是一个不错的前进方向
who are trying to to move their code to
谁试图将其代码移至
this to move their code away for example
例如，这可以移动他们的代码
from histories which for example has
来自历史，例如
been put into maintenance mode by by
由...进入维护模式
Netflix so if you're on it this is a
Netflix，因此，如果您使用它，这是一个
great opportunity to get off of it and
摆脱它的好机会
you can use history right there's
您可以使用历史记录
actually a hystrix implementation though
实际上是一个hystrix实现
I were I you I would start with
我是我，我将以
something like resilience for J if you
如果您有类似J的复原力
don't already have an investment in or
还没有投资或
dependency on hystrix I'll write with my
对hystrix的依赖性我将与我一起写
friends thanks for watching in it as
朋友感谢您的收看
always and we'll see you next time
总是，我们下次见
you
您